Finding Aid for the Herschel Burke Gilbert Papers PASC-M.0268
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Gilbert Personal Papers, Series 23.
  - Assorted Personal Papers (Box 288)
    Biographies, Resume and Background of Herschel Burke Gilbert; History of Laurel Record
- Accession LSC-2018-008 backlog material, LSC-2018-008; 4 Linear Feet 4 record cartons; 4 Audiovisual Carriers (4 film strips) (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  Scope and content
  Accession is comprised of recordings, music notes, correspondence, financial papers, contracts/agreements, scores and sheet music.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Unprocessed series. This material is unavailable for access. Please contact Special Collections reference (spec-coll@library.ucla.edu) for more information.